Happiness is a business
Little Joe is a drama, science fiction film directed by Jessica Hausner.
Alice, a single mother who is more dedicated to her work as a genetic engineer than to her teenage son Joe, develops a new variety
of flower that is supposed to have the ability to make its owner happy thanks to its special chemical properties.
Alice, played by Emily Beecham.
Chris, played by Ben Whishaw.
Bella, played by Kerry Fox.
Joe, played by Kit Connor.
Karl, played by David Wilmot.
Ric, played by Phénix Brossard.
Little Joe is a 2019 drama film co-written and directed by Jessica Hausner.
Starring Emily Beecham as Alice Woodard, a plant breeder and single mother who
creates "Little Joe", a plant that gives its caretakers joy.
The film had its world premiere at the main competition of the 2019 Cannes
Film Festival, where Beecham won the Best Actress award.
The film explores themes of co-workers relationship, genetic
engineering, woman director, mother son relationship.
The tone is emotional and thought_provoking.